import moment from 'moment';

const m1 = moment([2009, 6, 1]);
const m2 = moment();
const diff = moment.duration(m2.diff(m1));

export default {
  personality: 'MetalMusic',
  personalityId: 2,
  conversations: [
    {
      id: '1',
      parentId: '',
      question: `How metal are you?`,
      answer:
        'I am 100% authentic metal',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2',
      parentId: '',
      question: "What is your favourite metal band",
      answer: `My favourite metal band is Iron Maiden`,
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'How long have you been listening to metal songs?',
      answer: `I have been listening to metal songs since ${diff.years()} years now`,
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'What is your favourite metal song?',
      answer:
        "There is no such thing as favourite metal song, it all depends upon the metal album",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '5',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Do you play electric guitar?',
      answer:
        'No, I do covers of metal songs on classical guitar',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '6',
      parentId: '',
      question: "Do you know who is the founder of heavy metal?",
      answer:
        'The pioneers would be Led Zeppelin, Black Sabbath, Deep Purple',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '7',
      parentId: '',
      question: "How many bands have you listened to?",
      answer:
        'There are many bands , still uncountable',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '8',
      parentId: '',
      question: "Which metal genre do you like the most?",
      answer:
        'I am a Heavy Metal fan.',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '9',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'I see Iron Maiden logo on your tee, how many years have you followed them',
      answer:
        `I have been following Iron Maiden since ${diff.years()} years`,
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '10',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'I think rap and pop are much better than Metal music',
      answer:
        "I hate people who claim so, therefore you can just f**k off!",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '11',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Have you been to any Metal Band Tour?',
      answer:
        "Yes, I have been to one",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '12',
      parentId: '',
      question: 'Where can I buy authentic Metal Merchandise',
      answer: 'I would say buy it officially from the band\'s website',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: "You might be failing every Metal Detector test!!!",
      answer: 'That\'s true...!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'That\'s the best statement I\'ve ever heard!!!',
      answer:
        'Hahaaa...!!!!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'A human body consists of many other minerals, so basically you\'re not completely metal',
      answer: "Just shut the hell up, NERD",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '4-1',
      parentId: '1',
      question: 'I am more metal than you',
      answer:
        "Doesn\'t seem like that kid",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: "Never heard of it",
      answer:
        'You\'re way too ignorant, go explore the world more noob',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '2-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'Which album do you like the most?',
      answer:
        "I like The Number of the Beast, the most",
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'Which is your favourite song?',
      answer: 'Each album has a unique feature, there is no such thing as favourite song',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-2',
      parentId: '2',
      question: 'I prefer Linkin Park!',
      answer: 'That is not metal, it can\'t even be compared to rock, it is just pure bullshit',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'Wow!, that\'s a lot of years',
      answer: 'Yes, they are...',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '2-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question:
        'How many hours do you listen a day?',
      answer: 'I would say around 3 - 4 hours a day on an average',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'How did you hear about your first metal song?',
      answer:
        'I was randomly going through the cassettes and I found one of my favourite band',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-3',
      parentId: '3',
      question: 'You must be very old',
      answer: "No I am not, I just started listening young",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'So what\'s your favourite album?',
      answer:
        'I have many favourite albums which are specific to various bands',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '2-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question:
        'I think pop songs are much better',
      answer: 'You need to go to the rehab',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '3-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'You might be experienced with all this stuff',
      answer:
        'Yes , I am',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-4',
      parentId: '4',
      question: 'You\'re answer is incorrect',
      answer: 'You\'re incorrect to, perhaps your parents didn\'t correct you',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: "That seems weird",
      answer: 'I think that is unique',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question:
        'It is difficult to play metal songs on classical guitar',
      answer: 'It is difficult...!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: 'Do you play with an amp?',
      answer:
        'Sometimes, sometimes not',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-5',
      parentId: '5',
      question: "You can\'t do that",
      answer: 'I can do anything',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "Motorhead Lemmy was the founder of heavy metal",
      answer: 'No, he launched his band pretty late',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '2-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "Jesus Christ is the founder of heavy metal",
      answer:
        "You bet...!",
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: 'When was the first metal song made?',
      answer:
        'Iron Butterfly\'s debut album was titled as first heavy metal song',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-6',
      parentId: '6',
      question: "I don't like heavy metal",
      answer: 'I bet your parents don\'t like you as well',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: "Which band do you like the most?",
      answer: 'I am the biggest fan of Iron Maiden',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: 'You might have not listened to all the bands',
      answer: 'That might be possible',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: 'I think Justin Beiber is the greatest of them all',
      answer:
        'That noob is a piece of sh*t, there are many people in the world who shouldn\'t be born',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-7',
      parentId: '7',
      question: "Do you like pop?",
      answer: "No pop and rap suck",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: "That\'s awesome!",
      answer: 'Thanks',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: 'I like baby metal',
      answer: 'That just sucks, it is not even real metal',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '3-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: 'I don\'t like Heavy Metal',
      answer:
        'Maybe you can\'t handle Heavy Stuff',
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '4-8',
      parentId: '8',
      question: "Have you ever listened to any other genre other than Heavy Metal",
      answer: "Yes, I\'ve listened to almost all the other metal genres",
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '1-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: "That\'s a long term",
      answer: 'Yes, it is!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: 'When did Iron Maiden launch',
      answer: 'It started in 1975',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: 'How many members are there in Iron Maiden?',
      answer: 'Currently, there are 6 members in Iron Maiden',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-9',
      parentId: '9',
      question: "I follow Metallica",
      answer: "Metallica is not what it was in it\'s early years",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: "You are being rude",
      answer: 'Pop and Rap people are no brainers',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: 'Pop is still better than rap',
      answer: 'Both Pop and Rap should be flushed in the toilet',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '3-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: 'Why do you think so?',
      answer: 'I once listened to a pop song, and my ears started bleeding',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-10',
      parentId: '10',
      question: "You are wrong",
      answer: "I am always right regarding this topic",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
    {
      id: '1-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: "What was the tour?",
      answer: 'It was the Iron Maiden\'s heavy metal band tour',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: 'Where was the tour location?',
      answer: 'It was in Mumbai, India',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: 'I have\'nt gone to any tour',
      answer: 'You should go, it is a different experience',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '4-11',
      parentId: '11',
      question: "Have you also got any tour tee?",
      answer: "Indeed they do!",
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '1-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: "Great!",
      answer: 'Thanks!',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '2-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: 'I couldn\'t get some of the stuff in official website',
      answer: 'You can always query for help and check that out',
      mood: 'happy',
      sound: 'happy',
    },
    {
      id: '3-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: 'Have you got tour merchandise?',
      answer: 'Yes, some of them',
      mood: 'normal',
      sound: 'okay',
    },
    {
      id: '4-12',
      parentId: '12',
      question: "Official Websites are not so good",
      answer: "So do you prefer to buy unofficial merchandise?",
      mood: 'angry',
      sound: 'angry',
    },
  ],
};
